http://www.babies-and-sign-language.com/baby-signing-privacy-policy.html

Privacy Policy / Terms of Usage of www.babies-and-sign-language.com
"Babies and Sign Language" Privacy Policy
We recognize that your privacy is important. This document outlines
the types of personal information we receive and collect when you use
this Babies and Sign Language site. This document also outlines
some of the steps we take to safeguard information. We hope this will
help you make an informed decision about sharing personal information
with us.
Babies and Sign Language strives to maintain the highest
standards of decency, fairness and integrity in all our operations.
Likewise, we are dedicated to protecting our customers', consumers' and
online visitors' privacy on our website.
Personal Information
Babies and Sign Language collects personally identifiable
information from the visitors to our website only on a voluntary basis.
Personal information collected on a voluntary basis may include name,
postal address, email address, company name and telephone number.
This information is collected if you request information from us,
participate in a contest or sweepstakes, and sign up to join our email
list or request some other service or information from us. The
information collected is internally reviewed, used to improve the
content of our website, notify our visitors of updates, and respond to
visitor inquiries.
Once information is reviewed, it is discarded or stored in our files.
If we make material changes in the collection of personally identifiable
information we will inform you by placing a notice on our site.
Personal information received from any visitor will be used only for
internal purposes and will not be sold or provided to third parties.
Use of Cookies and Web Beacons
We may use cookies to help you personalize your online experience.
Cookies are identifiers that are transferred to your computer's hard
drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your
browser. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have
returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize the sites
pages, or register with any of our site's services, a cookie enables Babies and Sign Language to recall your specific information on subsequent visits.
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies by modifying your
Web browser; however, if you choose to decline cookies, you may not be
able to fully experience the interactive features of the site.
A web beacon is a transparent image file used to monitor your journey
around a single website or collection of sites. They are also referred
to as web bugs and are commonly used by sites that hire third-party
services to monitor traffic. They may be used in association with
cookies to understand how visitors interact with the pages and content
on the pages of a web site.
We may serve third party advertisements that use cookies and web
beacons in the course of ads being served on our web site to ascertain
how many times you've seen an advertisement. No personally identifiable
information you give us is provided to them for cookie or web beacon
use, so they cannot personally identify you with that information on our
web site.
Browsers can be set to accept or reject cookies or notify you when a
cookie is being sent. Privacy software can be used to override web
beacons. Taking either of these actions shouldn't cause a problem with
our site, should you so choose.
Google Advertising Cookie and Privacy Policies
Print
What is the DoubleClick DART cookie?
The DoubleClick DART cookie
is used by Google in the ads served on publisher websites displaying
AdSense for content ads. When users visit an AdSense publisher's website
and either view or click on an ad, a cookie may be dropped on that end
user's browser. The data gathered from these cookies will be used to
help AdSense publishers better serve and manage the ads on their site(s)
and across the web.
Google,
as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's
use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to
your users based on
their visit to your sites and other sites on
the Internet. Users
may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit
our website. These companies may use information (not including your
name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to
this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods
and services of interest to you. If you would like more information
about this practice and to know your choices about not having this
information used by these companies, click here.
Children's Online Privacy Protection Act
This website is directed to adults; it is not directed to children
under the age of 13. We operate our site in compliance with the
Children's Online Privacy Protection Act, and will not knowingly collect
or use personal information from anyone under 13 years of age.
Non-Personal Information
In some cases, we may collect information about you that is not
personally identifiable. We use this information, which does not
identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to
track users' movements around the site and to gather demographic
information about our user base as a whole. The information collected is
used solely for internal review and not shared with other organizations
for commercial purposes.
Release of Information
If Babies and Sign Language is sold, the information we have
obtained from you through your voluntary participation in our site may
transfer to the new owner as a part of the sale in order that the
service being provided to you may continue. In that event, you will
receive notice through our website of that change in control and
practices, and we will make reasonable efforts to ensure that the
purchaser honors any opt-out requests you might make of us.
How You Can Correct or Remove Information
We provide this privacy policy as a statement to you of our commitment
to protect your personal information. If you have submitted personal
information through our website and would like that information deleted
from our records or would like to update or correct that information,
please click use our Contact Us page.
Updates and Effective Date
Babies and Sign Language reserves the right to make changes
in this policy. If there is a material change in our privacy practices,
we will indicate on our site that our privacy practices have changed and
provide a link to the new privacy policy. We encourage you to
periodically review this policy so that you will know what information
we collect and how we use it.
Agreeing to Terms
If you do not agree to Babies and Sign Language Privacy Policy as posted here on this website, please do not use this site or any services offered by this site.
Your use of this site indicates acceptance of this privacy policy.
Hope you enjoy our site!
Free Baby Signing Chart!
Email
First Name
Then
Don't worry -- your e-mail address is totally secure.
I promise to use it only to send you Little Hands Express! Subscribe free to baby sign ezine!
Navigation
Home - Baby Signing
Baby Sign Language
What is Baby Signing?
Benefits of Baby Signs?
Who Else Benefits?
Baby Sign Language Stories
Parent Praises
Getting Started
How Do We Learn?
When Do We Start?
How Do We Sign?
How Do We Teach It?
International Baby Signs!
British Baby Signing (BSL)
Australian Baby Sign
French Sign Language
Italian Sign Language (ILS)
[?]Subscribe To This Site
Baby Sign Charts
Baby Sign Poster Set
New!
What's New?Join our RSS FeedsSuggestions/FeedbackAdd your Baby Signing Classes Advertise Your Baby Business or Company!
Just Ask!
Dear Mama Signs
Of the Months'
Story of the MonthPhoto of the MonthQuestion of the Month Vote/Poll of the Month
Share With Parents!
Show Off Your Baby Signing Picture!Share Your Baby Signing Experience!Submit your Baby Sign Classes
Site Sponsors
Click here to advertise on BabiesandSign.com!
Free Baby Sign Chart!
Email
First Name
Then
Don't worry -- your e-mail address is totally secure.
Baby Sign Language Home | About Us | Contact Us/Feedback
Articles | Baby Sign Language Benefits | Free Baby Signing
Glossary
Baby Sign Activities | Baby Signing Poster | Toddler Sign Language
Baby Signing Classes Near You |  What's New? | Webmasters / Affiliate Program | Research | FAQ| Privacy Policy
This babies and sign language website was made using TOP best software on earth!
© Little Hands Express 2006 -
Babies-and-Sign-Language.Com.
Remember our Baby Signing Website Easily!
www.learnbabysigning.com
Bookmark Our Baby Signing Site!
